And now we'll talk about the regular beam compliance
of council on the day of January 4, 2021.
So it's June 2, June 20, 15.
If I gave it five, five, five, five, five, five.
The free of three minutes from the December 15, 2020
regular beam.
So, in the beginning of August, I'm part of the meeting.
So, before that, we're going to have to take you to the next week,
we're going to talk about the number of five.
And number six is public influence,
let's get the personal care system.
And first, we're going to have a mark group.
Then we have a mark group.
Hello, my name is Mike Woodruff.
I'm kind of a coherent counsel with our heat and management
of heat and marketing and new views.
Probably, if you have, if you know me,
if I probably heard you, or if you see me on the internet,
it's March.
I have been talking about COVID-19 a lot.
The story gets deeper and deeper each time.
In addition to owning a business side of the better,
I spent eight years in the army.
One of the things of my job to do was be a built sanitation person,
basically, as responsible to make sure that soldiers were healthy.
And to prevent diseases and those kinds of things that happen.
As a matter of fact, our soldiers die on the battlefield from diseases
they do actually for what's involved.
So seeing this stuff that goes on right now,
yeah, I got some training on that years ago.
And so from a person who knows these things,
I really had a tough time talking about being in front of you,
because I'm a big guy.
I was told.
Top many years ago in college that you report the news. You don't make it.
And the other thing is to avoid it in the setting. Unfortunately, I have seen enough stuff going on
this community that I have to come before you all. If you thought about
I broke the 80s and when the TV show movies I watched back in the 80s was a movie called Red Dawn.
In which a foreign military came and invaded the United States. Everybody picked up the arms from
16 years old with above the fight the end of the war. If that happened today I could move during the
people in this room and would probably do that without question. Even to the point where we would
teach our children how this should be done. Every kid gets a Christmas for Christmas kids of
slingshot or of BB gun or whatever. We would have a conversation about doing conversations about
drinking is sacrifice on and on and on. Well, we have not been invaded by some kind of force with
bonds and airplanes that happen. But we have been invaded by a force. Who by 19? You can't see it?
Can't smell it? Can't taste it? Can't do anything. It's invisible but it's there. It's there to kill.
It doesn't care what the color of your skin is. It doesn't care about what you love. It doesn't care about
your social economic status. It doesn't care about who you're voting for. It kills. And so since we're at this
war with this virus, we need to pick up our arms and the arms is voting to have on our faces right now
this mask. It's the only way that we all can fight it. I am not a doctor. You're not a doctor. You might
be a doctor in the screen. But we can do the basic things where the mask wash our hands. Practice social
distancing. Be aware of our surroundings. Stay away from big groups of people. Sacrifice. It sucks.
I hate it. I want to go like the movies. I want to go eat and rest for my family. But until this is over,
it's done with. I'm not doing it. It's affected in my family. It's like everybody around. It's in the list.
You and myself. I just got over it. I'm probably the safest person. I'm the most cautious person.
So, anyway, if you believe in the right to like liberty and pursue happiness,
but the best thing you can do is wear this mask. Because if you don't, lower this, and stop it,
we all lose this thing. And we will pressure.
And so I, unfortunately, I will have to say, if there's a mandate, I'm all about it, because I'm going to have this mandate versus something a little more extreme.
We had an unemployment rate of 14% back in March.
You typically have 4%.
Right now we're hovering at 7%.
Lots of people are being victimized.
And if you can't wear a $5 mask and protect everybody around you,
that's your treatment.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, that's how I feel about it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Thank you, Richard.
I have to couple of concerns about the resolution of CC-2021.
A little bit of that is a not real sure or a normal understanding of how the coincides with the number four.
With that being, recommending that all citizens of businesses within the city of mind will follow the CC guidelines to prevent further spread of the COVID-19 virus,
pledging support to those business owners who required a use of masks or other CDC guidelines in the city of mind.
But as I flip the page, it says, for purposes of this resolution, if a person in the business within the city limits,
refuses to comply with the policies of that business, which immediately,
I think, shifts away from the CDC requirements into the policies of the business relating to COVID-19.
The business should request the person to comply with the premise.
Or, anyway, I read that the sign on the door, where it matters.
AT&T is doing a fantastic job with that.
As soon as you reach the front door, they say, if you have a no math, you can't be in it.
We all have that ability, whether it be the private sector, the municipality sector, state sector, tribal sector.
That's already in place.
There's other questions that arise in my mind is, if this is up to the businesses, that's one thing.
But if we're literally asking to follow the CDC guidelines, then we're asking for a full-fledged mask mandate.
Which brings that in, it brings that up actually up at a whole other scenario.
We flip over here.
You know, you start talking about social distancing.
Six feet or two more links apart.
We don't want to gather in large crowds.
You know, basically, CDC says that it needs a no problem.
It can be effective.
six hours. I mean I'm sorry to tell you that if that's a case then you know those chairs
there might be many ways so then there are your restaurants would have to follow this
man. You know the tables are perfect for six hours.
I totally get the important rate. I mean the private sector clients all they want. And I can
tell you that in the event and we go with clean mass demand they can use all that economically
in this area. There's just no value value. I mean it's in it's obvious. It's happening
right now. But there's no reason to go to such a drastic measure to say that we have to
have this. You know if you've been at a business owner once to stop you with the door
with the mass. Is that right? I can tell you that he wouldn't. I know there's a lot of
business owners that are not going to because they're suffering the way he did it's all
right. It'll kill the restaurants. But then again you already have people coming in the restaurants.
You have to have these on to be seated but then you take them off the heat. Most people don't even
wear them to go to the restaurant. But whatever they did they come back. You know it's to me I totally
get that everybody wants to get back to normal. But this is not the way to do it. The second thing
I came to my mind. Worst of all I believe it's all. Let's say that this thing which I know
it's not the pass and the event goes in both. There's just no way it can. It's not sensible.
The second thing is what? What an event it. Let's just say that I'm not up to speed on the wall.
I'm not trying to make some sort of systems the rest. I'm finally someone's right. And then
the police departments call. Then they come out. I mean who's going to basically pick up my
wallet. I think we should think about it. I think we should think about it. Thank you.
Thank you. It is a very well.
I think a little bit of a lot of lines of what. I can start it which is I'm a business owner. So I don't
have no health facility. I'm a counselor. So I need a few people who have been dealing with this
kind of pressure from this all year long but also with their whole life all the problems they've
already had. The people are on the edge. They're at the line. And so you're going to say that a business
owner is going to have to allow other customers to police their other customers and everyone's on fire.
And everyone's at that edge. We talked about this a couple of weeks ago. We said they don't have the police
force to mandate this and follow through with it. But we also said that we don't want to put our
officers in that kind of heat with the public in this comment back this time. But now you're suggesting
let's put the residents who are not properly trained.
We don't have to be escalated for on the edge who are frazzled, we're going to put them in there to look at their neighbor.
I'm sure we've all seen the YouTube's of the people at Walmart.
I have stores who have verbally attacked and assaulted and escalated into physical fights over masks and other towns and other states.
Pretty sure we've all seen it.
Is that what we want here?
We want to escalate that and do we want to escalate people?
We are already a poverty community.
So now let's take a business sonners.
Let's run the amount of business which is what we're going to last, which isn't very much.
I mean, I also own property, I don't know, commercial building.
So now you're going to possibly cause my renter to not be able to pay their rent to me.
So it's their businesses and then it's the end.
Then I'm a residential property member.
And those people have to pay their rent.
Which means they have to have a job to pay that rent.
This is in so many different dynamics.
Yes, we talked about sacrifice.
Whose sacrifice is that?
Is children over here talked about?
He doesn't eat at restaurants.
He doesn't go to movie theater switch.
By the way, my husband, the theater is closing down right now.
And they're in their 50s, where they should be thinking about retirement.
And they're completely wiped out.
Okay, so if this is not just about selflessness, it's certain areas.
This should be about everybody's well-being, not just some people.
Because many people were covered.
Like he said, he just recovered.
He doesn't go to restaurants.
He doesn't go to movies.
He always wears this mask.
And he got it.
I've recovered from it.
I had a headache for two days.
My children never had a symptom.
Am I not even through a grandmother?
I've gotten a million achievement in the hospital for six days.
And she's recovering at home.
I don't wear a mask.
I have not changed my life.
I respect others.
If your mask works, I say six feet from you.
I don't see the issue in that.
I just find an interesting thing that we're talking about sacrifice in the mask.
But yet, people are still getting sick.
And they're still recovering.
People are still recovering.
I don't know how my life has been recovered.
I'm shutting you off business this down.
Right now, the unemployment's working because they're being pushed with that extra money.
But when that money dries up, it won't.
What do we left with?
And do you want to be the business owner?
That has that quite huge store.
It loses oil customers because they feel their rights provided.
And they don't come back.
They can't even go to job the right now.
I do whatever they want.
And the taxes are low.
And they have more selection.
So we're going to already take our higher taxes in our lack of selection.
And then we're going to force this down.
People start saying, never going to put the endanger of somebody starting to bite with them.
Inside the business.
But that we're talking about shop local.
We're talking about encouraging the economy.
I don't think you guys have really considered this very well.
When you're talking about citizens of rest and mass mandate.
In a community that's shown you how they feel about mass mandate.
Those who want to wear it wear it.
And those who do not.
They're the right.
Thank you.
and the Center did it.
Thank you very much.
Great to have you have some prepared things that are
to be table and out there.
I mean, yeah, just one of us do,
who had no animal at all.
It's different.
Why does that would be thing one?
I'm just not sure.
But I'll talk about last two years.
Oh, yeah.
You can talk about again.
So you can move, motion to the three
Senate gender set for I am a candidate for the five of the next.
So, we're going to take you.
Second.
Thank you.
All right.
The 13 will also be table.
In office.
And I'm 15.
Resolution C.C.
21.
That's your two.
We're getting them also.
And this is.
We're getting the same.
All right.
Okay.
Thank you.
I think we're going to.
Okay.
Well, I.
I understand a.
Respected is too early going from on this.
And I asked this.
It would be convenient.
And the.
Was.
So I don't feel as though it's in French you could want anybody's rights.
It's honestly just giving like those that stand on the do one.
That's within this way.
So this is what is not on that right right now.
No, no, no, no, no.
They do have that right to it.
Yes, but this gives a little bit of teeth to them.
I'm not debating the fact that we need to have a mandate for all businesses.
This is specifically for those that do want to have our national facilities.
So it really is just an expression of showing support to those local merchants because this is the school's department.
I think I need to have.
Well, some of the comments that we have about citizens of the rest.
This only allows the business and stuff where they're designated employees to make a citizens of the rest.
It's basically the same format that is used for instance in Walmart or shopping.
John, do you citizen doesn't make a citizens of rest.
There is the employees of the school.
There's a lot of legal reasons why you do it by way of assistance to the rest of it.
That's really relevant to the conversation.
But it's not a matter of test terms policing the other customers,
but a matter of the other main thing is it's only if the store itself wants to do that.
And making that decision, if business decides, you know, will this run off some test version?
Or will it be another test version?
It might.
But that's a decision for business on a loan to make that decision.
Can't they make that decision already?
I mean, it's already.
So I don't think that's not sure.
I don't think so.
I don't think that's not sure.
I don't think that's on the lead, but usually a couple of days before we were at Gassio-Lett's,
I have to take care of Gassio.
I'm not sure.
It's a lead.
So, I don't think that's already in place.
But I don't know how badly we need to be.
My water's here and creating something else.
But the things we were really confusing to settle on our business is a company today.
So I have looked at the actual month visited.
You know, if we get loud, they use 16 year old kid,
your own kid, your fault grades, your built-in system,
and rest of them, you know, if that's
your own grades, that's your own grades.
You don't, you're saying you're in hell,
but you can't come to the end of the day.
The end is the day you might forget about the car,
but watch the door, and someone tells them
that I'm a math dog, you know?
So now there's gonna be a lot of the flat,
and that kid gets to find the question line.
Over math, and that's the length,
and they're just a well, the city's that we've been doing.
That's part of the liability issue,
the business, the size, he makes the citizens of the race.
Who, which of their employees or business
are having to do it?
It's not the cities, it's not the scope.
The same thing, at the end, they're all armed.
We do not have to do this.
So they're all armed.
Our officers do not risk all armed risks,
and they can transfer to the US to the US.
All armed have the security board.
They actually have security officers.
That's all part of the decision factor
that the business needs to get there.
And then schools of problem,
and I got to call for our superintendent of schools today
saying, what that gives this, the way you're contacted about this.
I'm not gonna laugh at this, you'd call all day.
He said, I'll score it, you gotta do it,
and he said, I try to know more about it,
or I'm gonna give it something, and I don't know that.
Well, that is up threat, because the I've come up,
there's actually a female chain between the I,
about this before we're gonna protect your threat,
because that's part of the conversation.
What you want in this risk, which?
So you call me it for a while today,
and I'll add it to the code.
I think you'll have to tell you the easy one, child.
I think you're overstepping here, I think our citizens have told us time and time and time and time again what they want.
Here we are.
It's voted in representative representative community and we normed over and over.
They're voices being spoken.
And we're trying to calm them and throw the lead on.
We're going to listen to them and give them what they want.
I guess when I heard what the business was looking at, you know,
we've got the constituents who on this side do not want them else to make a non-stop direction.
We're going.
But those businesses, those businesses that are only something for them at least,
again, something to keep to it.
They would allow them to, I mean, yes, that might be our idea that this just gives them a number of
different standards.
And I was trying to brush them out for two questions for you.
Or I'm not sure.
Didn't we pass the resolution just a couple of weeks ago of hour and an hour and an hour before
folks didn't best again to follow CDC stuff?
That resolution is not at all.
They have urged people to follow the CDC guidance.
Yes.
Er...
I'm curious about it.
And secondly, if there's anything about this resolution, other than some language,
but is there anything with the teeth involved in all,
that doesn't already currently exist in the wall, somebody's not being am ago in our local business?
That is a very legitimate question.
My answer, the rest of the legal perspective, which I've said,
is the answer to the order.
My answer would be that the Dan, all right.
I think it was, that's number four deaths.
A lot.
I don't want to speak with them, but just to show you the most businesses that
they've got to do it that we would stand up.
Right.
Well, I'd spoken with some constituents and say,
call it a city that for city facilities.
That's part of this resolution.
Which could be applied in the same way.
It would be an individual agreement with the State of the League of the Mito.
I guess it's not directly to which it is in the rest of the rest of the rest,
nor on the State facilities.
But in the same sense, if it's going to happen to the State of the League,
the State of the League, you will not support those businesses.
They're also Microsoft.
That's different than the right or a few service.
And then some more.
And then to somebody doesn't believe in maybe between you, please, in service, we can call the cops then and say they're refusing to leave.
Well, I was thinking that the city has done this, something happened.
The city is still there.
Is it not fit for us to support the community business?
And that's what I say.
So it's not a cycle one.
It's not a business that they don't want it.
This is not.
Correct.
But the ones that I have observed in families that have made research, people were very young,
and I know that we both played there a little bit frustrated.
They got a little problem.
There's a big problem.
People are using to wear masks and medicine.
They're using to.
That's the last time I talked with a cheap, high-power, which was last week.
And you would think that it was a conversation about the medicine.
I don't know where I stand.
And I make a motion to approve it.
I'll second the motion that we vote.
Can you hear me?
No.
Pardon?
I'm 16.
New business with the business.
It's because of the vision that I'm 17 there.
You can see that.
I'd like to welcome our new city manager, Maurice.
It was first day on job.
And I'll take a picture here today.
I'm probably a little overwhelmed.
We'll do one more.
And I'll be okay.
And I'm really productive.
I also want to thank all our clients.
I deserve this.
Our interview for the last six months or so.
They're really good job for us.
that he's inspired by the grandfather passed away
to say prayer for his family,
but he didn't appreciate one thing, yeah.
So, look forward to the future.
Thank you, Mr. Mayer.
We're able to be here in my family,
and I've re-located my life, I've been here just before Thanksgiving.
We've gotten several days.
I could not wait for it today.
So, I had a great day,
nothing to make with you are great,
but I'm going to use it, of course,
it's different fault to get the number of new staff.
You know, the realization of this size,
and you've got the issues that we have,
and you've been trying to social distance with me.
We respect both, but we will find the way
to use technology when I can,
and the problems to communicate with all of our employees
and to be with the council and be available.
For anyone who is really my best,
to observe the great citizens of town,
I love so much, and you really be back,
and I appreciate the warm welcome,
and we're forward to talking with everybody.
Need to buy assistance anyway?
Before I direct up today,
I get what to give the glory and opportunity
to be introduced to the living, or do we have?
Now, I just like to let you all be aware
that the form of law, laws, has been working
at 10 times under the means of the great living,
false nester, and start a spring semester.
He's doing a lot of research, particularly the high-old research.
He's not a law student at this point,
but he is going to go into law school at the University of London.
And he's not a lot of help.
One of the agenda items that the government,
you're saying, we did a lot of work on that,
so I just went, but let you all know
that you've been near and helping out.
Thank you.
Now, we're 18, so you're having a vacation.
You already did it?
I don't know, but I think the government will move.
Second.
Hey, this is not appropriate.
Time to turn it up.